Guide to the Northern Pacific Railway Company Records 1870-1968
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Engineering Department, 1870-1968; Subgroup 1; 165.25 linear feet and 14 oversize volumes
  - Pacific Division (Oregon/Washington), 1871-1909; Series XIII; 4.5 linear feet and 1 oversize volume
    This series contains construction documents generated by the Pacific Division of the NPRR, operating in western Oregon and Washington. Land acquisition correspondence, construction proposals and estimates, subsidiary line communications, and maps predominate the series. Bound volumes include outgoing correspondence from station engineers, financial records (such as frieght bills, transaction ledgers, and station maintenance vouchers) and personnel documents.
    - General Correspondence, Land Acquisitions, 1898 (Box-folder 202/1)
    - General Correspondence, Bridges, 1901 - 1905 (Box-folder 202/2)
    - General Correspondence, Cascade Canal Company, 1903-07 - 1904-05 (Box-folder 202/3)
    - General Correspondence, Employments, 1907 - 1908 (Box-folder 202/4)
    - General Correspondence, Work Train, Vancouver, Washington, 1907 - 1908 (Box-folder 202/5)
    - General Correspondence, Vancouver-Kalama line, Woodland and Richfield, 1906 - 1908 (Box-folder 202/6)
    - General Correspondence, Fairfax Branch, 1901 - 1903 (Box-folder 202/7)
    - Estimates of Engineering Department, 1895 - 1897 (Box-folder 203/1)
    - Estimates of Engineering Department, 1897 - 1905 (Box-folder 203/2)
    - Approximate Monthly Estimates, 1904 - 1906 (Box-folder 203/3)
    - Estimates at Eagle Gorge, 1902 (Box-folder 203/4)
    - Reports, Work Train, 1908 (Box-folder 203/5)
    - Maps, 1903 (Box-folder 203/6)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1872-02 - 1872-10 (Box-volume 204/236)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, R.R. Randall, 1872-05 - 1872-11 (Box-volume 204/237)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D.C. Sinsley, W.M. Roberts, 1872-09 - 1874-03 (Box-volume 204/238)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Work at Kalama, Hunters, and Goble (Washington), 1889-12 - 1890-08 (Box-volume 204/239)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1890-06 - 1891-02 (Box-volume 205/240)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Work at Kalama, Hunters, and Goble (Washington), 1890-08 - 1892-02 (Box-volume 205/241)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, B.B. Kelliher, 1891-01 - 1891-03 (Box-volume 205/242)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Edison Shops (Washington), C.S. Bibler, 1891-02 - 1891-08 (Box-volume 205/243)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, M.H. Bedofe, 1891-05 - 1891-07 (Box-volume 205/244)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J.M. Willard, 1891-05 - 1891-09 (Box-volume 206/245)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Edison Shops (Washington), C.S. Bibler, 1891-08 - 1893-03 (Box-volume 206/246)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J.M. Willard, 1891-09 - 1892-03 (Box-volume 206/247)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J.M. Willard, 1891-10 - 1892-01 (Box-volume 206/248)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Vancouver, Washington, A.F. Statler, 1906-06 - 1906-12 (Box-volume 206/249)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Vancouver, Washington, W.C. Taylor, 1906-11 - 1907-05 (Box-volume 207/250)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Vancouver, Washington, A.F. Statler, 1908-11 - 1909-05 (Box-volume 207/251)
    - Supply Ledger, 1882-12 - 1884-04 (Box-volume 207/252)
    - Ledger, Puyallup Yard (Washington), 1883-04 - 1884-01 (Box-volume 207/253)
    - Vouchers and Estimates, circa 1871-02 - 1871-11 (Box-volume 208/254)
    - Freight Bills, 1883-10 - 1885-01 (Box-volume 208/255)
    - Local Bills, Tacoma, Washington, 1885-08 - 1887-03 (Box-volume 208/256)
    - Certified Bills, Tacoma, Washington, 1890 (Box-volume 208/257)
    - Certified Bills and Copies of Estimates, 1889 - 1890 (Box-volume 208/258)
    - Distribution Records, Edison Shops (Washington), 1891 (Box-volume 208/259)
    - Record of Expense Bills, E. H. McHenry, 1891-06 - 1892-07 (Volume 260)
    - Bills and Vouchers, 1907-10 - 1907-12 (Box-volume 209/261)
    - Force Account Bills, 1907-12 - 1908-09 (Box-volume 209/262)
    - Bills and Invoices, 1908-09 - 1909-06 (Box-volume 209/263)
    - Rental Collections, 1895 (Box-volume 209/264)
    - Material Received in Cars, Edison Yard (Washington), 1891-02 - 1891-08 (Box-volume 210/265)
    - Requisitions and Distribution of Pay Rolls for Kalama Inclines, Work at Hunters and Goble (Washington), 1889-12 - 1891-02 (Box-volume 210/266)
  - Portland Division (Oregon/Washington), 1881-1909; Series XIV; 1.25 linear feet
    This series contains bound volumes of outgoing correspondence and financial records from the Portland Division of the NPRR, operating in western Oregon and southern Washington.
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1883-03 - 1884-06 (Box-volume 211/267)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1883-06 - 1884-04 (Box-volume 211/268)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J. T. Mitchell, 1883-12 - 1884-11 (Box-volume 211/269)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, W. C. Taylor, 1908-06 - 1909-04 (Box-volume 212/270)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Telegrams, 1883-03 - 1884-09 (Box-volume 212/271)
    - Cash Book, 1881-11 - 1882-04 (Box-volume 212/272)
    - Train Order Book, 1883-10 - 1885-02 (Box-volume 212/273)
    - Manifest of Material Shipped, 1883-04 - 1884-01 (Box-volume 213/274)
    - Supplies and Materials, 1883-12 - 1886-01 (Box-volume 213/275)
    - Time Book, 1884-05 - 1884-06 (Box-volume 213/276)
  - Seattle Division (Oregon/Washington), 1901-1905; Series XV; 0.25 linear feet
    This series contains two folders of construction correspondence and design maps created by the Seattle Division of the NPRR.
    - General Correspondence, Construction, 1901-12 - 1905-06 (Box-folder 214/1)
    - Maps, 1904, 1905 (Box-folder 214/2)
  - Western Division (Oregon/Washington), 1883-1907; Series XVI; 4.0 linear feet and 1 oversize volume
    This series contains general correspondence, financial, and personnel records generated by the Western Division of the NPRR, operating in western and central Washington state. Most records in this series concern construction and maintenance projects, providing extensive details about instrumentation, materials used, work force needs, and station operations. Intensive projects documented in this series include the Hoquiam extension near Tacoma, various coal bunkers in central Washington, and reconstruction of the "Georgie Oaks" steamboat on the Columbia River. This series also includes extensive documentation of negotiations with subcontractors and unaffiliated rail lines. Most materials in this series were generated by the Tacoma Branch; however, other units are represented (such as the Clealum, Centralia, Columbia River, and Eagle Gorge branches).
    - General Correspondence, 1897-05 - 1904-08 (Box-folder 215/1)
    - General Correspondence, Hoquiam Extension, Tacoma, Washington, 1895, 1987-1898 (Box-folder 215/2)
    - General Correspondence, Hoquiam Extension, Tacoma, Washington, 1898-03 - 1898-06 (Box-folder 215/3)
    - General Correspondence, Hoquiam Extension, Tacoma, Washington, 1898-07 - 1898-09 (Box-folder 215/4)
    - General Correspondence, Hoquiam Extension, Tacoma, Washington, 1898-10 - 1898-12 (Box-folder 215/5)
    - General Correspondence, Hoquiam Extension, Tacoma, Washington, 1899-01 - 1907-01 (Box-folder 215/6)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1901-01 - 1901-05 (Box-folder 216/1)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1901-06 - 1901-12 (Box-folder 216/2)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1902-01 - 1902-08 (Box-folder 216/3)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1902-09 - 1903-09 (Box-folder 216/4)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1903-10 - 1905-01 (Box-folder 216/5)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1905-02 - 1905-05 (Box-folder 216/6)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1905-06 - 1905-12 (Box-folder 216/7)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1906-01 - 1906-04 (Box-folder 216/8)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1906-05 - 1906-09 (Box-folder 217/1)
    - General Correspondence, Instruments, Tacoma Branch, 1906-10 - 1907-02 (Box-folder 217/2)
    - General Correspondence, Coal Bunkers - Castle Rock and Carbonado, Washington, 1889, 1893 - 1899 (Box-folder 217/3)
    - General Correspondence, Accounting, Tacoma Branch, 1897, 1901 - 1902 (Box-folder 217/4)
    - General Correspondence, Coal Bunkers, Clealum Branch, 1889, 1893 - 1899 (Box-folder 217/5)
    - General Correspondence, Coal Bunkers and Hannaford Creek Bridge, Centralia Branch, 1897-04 - 1902-02 (Box-folder 217/6)
    - General Correspondence, Columbia River Branch, 1900-10 - 1902-08 (Box-folder 218/1)
    - General Correspondence, Engineers Office, 1883-03 - 1887-05 (Box-folder 218/2)
    - General Correspondence, Carbonado-Fairfax line, 1900-11-13 - 1901-04-30 (Box-folder 218/3)
    - General Correspondence, Carbonado-Fairfax line, 1901-05 - 1901-09 (Box-folder 218/4)
    - General Correspondence, Rebuilding of "Georgie Oakes" Steamboat, 1904-01 - 1905-03 (Box-folder 218/5)
    - General Correspondence, Rebuilding of "Georgie Oakes" Steamboat, 1905-04 - 1907-03 (Box-folder 218/6)
    - Disbursement of Expenses, various lines, 1887-01 - 1887-05 (Box-folder 218/7)
    - Disbursement of Expenses, various lines, 1887-07 - 1887-10 (Box-folder 218/8)
    - General Correspondence, Construction of Log Culvert at Beaver Lake, Washington, 1900-05 (Box-folder 219/1)
    - General Correspondence, Location of Post Offices, 1900-07-28 - 1900-10-03 (Box-folder 219/2)
    - General Correspondence, Contracts, 1899-07 - 1901-03 (Box-folder 219/3)
    - General Correspondence, Contracts, 1901-04 - 1905-05 (Box-folder 219/4)
    - General Correspondence, Columbia and Puget Sound Railroad Crossing and Connection at Henry's Switch (Washington), 1899-07 - 1900-09 (Box-folder 219/5)
    - General Correspondence, Columbia and Puget Sound Railroad Crossing and Connection at Henry's Switch (Washington), 1900-10 - 1903-07 (Box-folder 219/6)
    - General Correspondence, Progress of Work, 1899-08-15 - 1900-08-13 (Box-folder 219/7)
    - General Correspondence, Green River Construction Company, Tracking Contract and Supply Cars, 1899-03 - 1900-04 (Box-folder 219/8)
    - General Correspondence, Green River Construction Company, Tracking Contract and Supply Cars, 1900-05 - 1901-03 (Box-folder 219/9)
    - General Correspondence, Shipments of Outfits and Materials, 1899-08-12 - 1900-01-30 (Box-folder 219/10)
    - General Correspondence, Shipments of Outfits and Materials, 1900-02 - 1901-08 (Box-folder 219/11)
    - General Correspondence, Operation of Line, 1900-03 - 1900-11 (Box-folder 219/12)
    - General Correspondence, Crushed Rock and Sand Supply, 1899-09 - 1900-02 (Box-folder 219/13)
    - Time Reports, 1900-07 - 1900-08 (Box-folder 220/1)
    - Time Reports, 1900-08 - 1901-01 (Box-folder 220/2)
    - Force Reports, 1899-07-22 - 1899-09-09 (Box-folder 220/3)
    - Force Reports, 1899-09-16 - 1899-10-14 (Box-folder 220/4)
    - Force Reports, 1899-10-21 - 1899-11-25 (Box-folder 220/5)
    - Force Reports, 1899-12 - 1900-03 (Box-folder 220/6)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, C. S. Prowell, 1883-04 - 1884-01 (Box-folder 221/277)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, L. M. German, 1883-10 - 1884-01 (Box-folder 221/278)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, South Prairie, Washington, James Rogers, 1884-11-05 - 1884-11-26 (Box-volume 221/279)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Eagle Gorge Branch, J. L. Smith, 1887-04 - 1887-06 (Volume 280)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Eagle Gorge Branch, 1886-06 - 1886-11 (Box-volume 221/281)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Eagle Gorge Branch, 1886-12 - 1887-03 (Box-volume 221/282)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Eagle Gorge Branch, A. Wold, 1887-04 - 1887-12 (Box-volume 222/283)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Copalis, Washington, C.C. Van Arsdol, 1900-09 - 1901-04 (Box-volume 222/284)
    - Financial Records, Order Book, 1884-04 - 1884-09 (Box-volume 222/285)
  - Yakima Division (Oregon/Washington), 1883-1889; Series XVII; 1.5 linear feet
    This series contains bound volumes of outgoing correspondence and financial records from the Yakima Division of the NPRR.
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1884-09 - 1885-01 (Box-volume 223/286)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J. L. Smith, 1884-10 - 1884-12 (Box-volume 223/287)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, H. S. Hinson, 1885-02 - 1885-07 (Box-volume 223/288)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1885-07 - 1886-01 (Box-volume 224/289)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1886-03 - 1887-11 (Box-volume 224/290)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Ellensburg, Washington, 1886-04 - 1887-04 (Box-volume 224/291)
    - Financial Ledger, 1883-10 - 1884-02 (Box-volume 224/292)
    - Engineers Report of Material, 1885 (Box-volume 224/293)
    - Requisitions for Construction, Kennewick-Pasco Bridge, 1887-04 - 1889-01 (Box-volume 225/294)
    - Time Book, 1885-04 - 1887-08 (Box-volume 225/295)
    - Time Book, 1885-05 (Box-volume 225/296)
    - Record of Progress, Profiles, and Track Reports, 1884 - 1885 (Box-volume 225/297)
    - Wood Record, 1884-10 - 1885-03 (Box-volume 225/298)
  - Dakota Division, 1883-1910; Series XVIII; 2.25 linear feet
    This series contains bound volumes of outgoing correspondence and financial records from the Dakota Division of the NPRR. Materials in this series particularly highlight operations in the communities of Valley City, Sykeston, and Jamestown, North Dakota, and Glendive, Montana.
    - General Correspondence, 1907-01-26 - 1907-05-20 (Box-folder 226/1)
    - General Correspondence, 1907-06-01 - 1907-06-19 (Box-folder 226/2)
    - General Correspondence, 1907-07-01 - 1907-07-31 (Box-folder 226/3)
    - General Correspondence, 1907-08-01 - 1907-08-19 (Box-folder 226/4)
    - General Correspondence, 1907-08-20 - 1907-09-30 (Box-folder 226/5)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Jamestown, North Dakota, 1883-07 - 1883-10 (Box-volume 227/299)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Sykeston, North Dakota, 1899-04 - 1899-09 (Box-volume 227/300)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Valley City, North Dakota, 1906-03 - 1907-03 (Box-volume 228/301)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Valley City, North Dakota, 1907-03 - 1907-06 (Box-volume 228/302)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Valley City, North Dakota, 1907-06 - 1907-09 (Box-volume 228/303)
    - General Correspondence, Valley City, North Dakota, 1907-09 - 1908-01 (Box-volume 228/304)
    - General Correspondence, Valley City, North Dakota, 1907-09 - 1908-11 (Box-volume 229/305)
    - General Correspondence, Valley City, North Dakota, 1910-01 - 1910-06 (Box-volume 229/306)
    - Financial Ledger, Yellowstone River Bridge, Glendive, Montana, undated (Box-volume 229/307)
    - Car Report, Valley City, North Dakota, 1907-10 - 1908-01 (Box-volume 229/308)
  - Minnesota Division, 1881-1960; Series XIX; 7.5 linear feet
    This series contains correspondence and financial records from the Minnesota Division of the NPRR. Materials include extensive correspondence and financial records generated by operations in Dilworth, Muskoda, and Fergus Falls, Minnesota. This series also includes detailed construction and maintenance records, traffic reports, and vendor contracts.
    - General Correspondence, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1906-05-24 - 1906-07-06 (Box-folder 230/1)
    - General Correspondence, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1906-07-07 - 1906-08-10 (Box-folder 230/2)
    - General Correspondence, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1906-08-11 - 1906-09-19 (Box-folder 230/3)
    - General Correspondence, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1906-09-20 - 1906-11-02 (Box-folder 230/4)
    - General Correspondence, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1906-11-03 - 1903-12-10 (Box-folder 230/5)
    - General Correspondence, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1906-12-11 - 1907-03-07 (Box-folder 230/6)
    - General Correspondence, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1907-03-08 - 1907-06 (Box-folder 230/7)
    - General Correspondence, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1907-06-04 - 1907-11-22 (Box-folder 230/8)
    - General Correspondence, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1907-11-22 - 1908-01-01 (Box-folder 230/9)
    - Expense Reports, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1906-07 - 1907-03 (Box-folder 231/1)
    - Expense Reports, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1907-04 - 1907-07 (Box-folder 231/2)
    - Expense Reports, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1907-08 - 1907-09 (Box-folder 231/3)
    - Expense Reports, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1907-09-24 - 1907-09-30 (Box-folder 231/4)
    - Expense Reports, Dilworth, Minnesota, 1907-10 - 1908-01 (Box-folder 231/5)
    - General Correspondence, Muskoda, Minnesota, 1902-06 - 1904-07 (Box-folder 231/6)
    - General Correspondence, Muskoda, Minnesota, 1907-02 - 1907-11 (Box-folder 231/7)
    - General Correspondence, Muskoda, Minnesota, 1908-04 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 231/8)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Fergus Falls, Minnesota, Campbell, 1881-04 - 1881-10 (Box-volume 232/309)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Fergus Falls, Minnesota, Kimball, 1882-04 - 1882-06 (Box-volume 232/310)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Fergus Falls, Minnesota, Kimball, 1882-06 - 1882-09 (Box-volume 232/311)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Fergus Falls, Minnesota, Kimball, 1882-09-1882-12 (Box-volume 232/312)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Fergus Falls, Minnesota, Kimball, 1882-12 - 1883-03 (Box-volume 232/313)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Minneapolis, Minnesota, Kimball, 1887-04 - 1889-05 (Box-volume 233/314)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Fergus Falls, Minnesota, Kimball, 1891-10 - 1892-04 (Box-volume 233/315)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, St. Paul, Minnesota, Vander Horck, 1903-09 - 1904-02 (Box-volume 233/316)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, St. Paul, Minnesota, Fred Browne, 1906-11 - 1907-06 (Box-volume 233/317)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, Lake City, Minnesota, Loomis, 1910-06 - 1910-08 (Box-volume 233/318)
    - Financial Journal, 1887-04 - 1888-01 (Box-volume 234/319)
    - Bills and Statements, 1881-07 - 1882-12 (Box-volume 234/320)
    - Estimates and Bills, 1883-02 - 1884-02 (Box-volume 234/321)
    - Force Bills, 1911-10 - 1912-04 (Box-volume 234/322)
    - Station Requisitions, 1895-01 - 1896-06 (Box-volume 234/323)
    - Records of Track Laying, 1904-08 - 1904-09 (Box-volume 235/324)
    - Records of Gravel Received, 1903-02 - 1903-05 (Box-volume 235/325)
    - Drafting Room, Notes and Surveys, 1881-06 - 1882-12 (Box-volume 235/326)
    - General Correspondence, 1903 (Box-folder 236/1)
    - General Correspondence, 1903 - 1906 (Box-folder 236/2)
    - General Correspondence, 1904 (Box-folder 236/3)
    - General Correspondence, 1905 (Box-folder 236/4)
    - General Correspondence, 1905 (Box-folder 236/5)
    - General Correspondence, 1905 (Box-folder 236/6)
    - General Correspondence, 1944 (Box-folder 236/7)
    - General Correspondence, 1945 (Box-folder 237/1)
    - General Correspondence, 1945 (Box-folder 237/2)
    - General Correspondence, 1946 (Box-folder 237/3)
    - General Correspondence, 1960 (Box-folder 237/4)
    - Reports and Contracts, Minnesota Specification Reports, 1944 (Box-folder 237/5)
    - Reports and Contracts, Minnesota Specification Reports, 1945 (Box-folder 237/6)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1940's - 1950's (Box-folder 237/7)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1942 (Box-folder 238/1)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1942 - 1957 (Box-folder 238/2)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1946 - 1953 (Box-folder 238/3)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1948 (Box-folder 238/4)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1948 - 1953 (Box-folder 238/5)
    - Reports and Contracts, Coal Contracts, 1950's (Box-folder 239/1)
    - Reports and Contracts, Coal Contracts, 1950's (Box-folder 239/2)
    - Reports and Contracts, Coal Contracts, 1950's (Box-folder 239/3)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1950's (Box-folder 239/4)
    - Reports and Contracts, Iron Casting Contracts, 1950's (Box-folder 239/5)
    - Reports and Contracts, Brass Bearings and Casting Contracts, 1951 - 1954 (Box-folder 239/6)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1953 - 1957 (Box-folder 240/1)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1953 (Box-folder 240/2)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1954 (Box-folder 240/3)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1958 (Box-folder 240/4)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1913 (Box-folder 240/5)
    - Reports and Contracts, Dakota Division Records, 1890 - 1901 (Box-folder 241/1)
    - Reports and Contracts, Dakota Division Records, 1905 (Box-folder 241/2)
    - Reports and Contracts, Dakota Division Records, 1905 (Box-folder 241/3)
    - Reports and Contracts, Dakota Division Records, 1905 (Box-folder 241/4)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1946 (Box-folder 241/5)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1946 (Box-folder 241/6)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1946 (Box-folder 241/7)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1946 (Box-folder 242/1)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1947 (Box-folder 242/2)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1947 (Box-folder 242/3)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1947 (Box-folder 242/4)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1947 (Box-folder 242/5)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1948 (Box-folder 242/6)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1948 (Box-folder 242/7)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1948 (Box-folder 243/1)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1948 (Box-folder 243/2)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1949 (Box-folder 243/3)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1949 (Box-folder 243/4)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1949 (Box-folder 243/5)
    - Reports and Contracts, 1949 (Box-folder 243/6)
  - Wisconsin Division, 1881-1893; Series XX; 2.5 linear feet
    This series contains outgoing correspondence and financial records from the Wisconsin Division of the NPRR. Correspondence and financial records were primarily generated by F.W.D. Holbrook, the division engineer. Financial records include operation summaries and construction estimates.
    - Omaha Junction to Conner's Point, Estimates of Costs, 1883-07 - 1883-09 (Box-folder 244/1)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1881 - 1884 (Box-volume 244/327)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1882-03 - 1882-06 (Box-volume 244/328)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1882-06 - 1882-09 (Box-volume 244/329)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1882-09 - 1883-01 (Box-volume 244/330)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1883-02 - 1883-06 (Box-volume 245/331)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1883-07 - 1883-09 (Box-volume 245/332)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1883-09 - 1883-11 (Box-volume 245/333)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1883-11 - 1884-02 (Box-volume 245/334)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1884 (Box-volume 246/335)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1884-07 - 1884-11 (Box-volume 246/336)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J. Dewar, 1884-09 - 1885-03 (Box-volume 246/337)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J. Dewar, 1884-12 - 1885-05 (Box-volume 246/338)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, J.B. Clough, 1885-01 - 1885-03 (Box-volume 246/339)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, D. Armitage and C. Clough, 1885-01 - 1885-03 (Box-volume 247/340)
    - Records of Bills Against Wisconsin Central, 1892-12 - 1893-02 (Box-volume 247/341)
    - Financial Records, Statistics, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1883 (Box-volume 247/342)
    - Financial Records, Statistics, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1884 (Box-volume 247/343)
    - Contractors Estimates, 1881-06 - 1883-09 (Box-volume 247/344)
    - Construction Estimates, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1882 - 1883 (Box-volume 247/345)
    - Construction Estimates, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1882 - 1883 (Box-volume 248/346)
    - Construction Estimates, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1883 (Box-volume 248/347)
    - Construction Estimates, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1883 (Box-volume 248/348)
    - Construction Estimates, F.W.D. Holbrook, 1883 - 1884 (Box-volume 248/349)
    - Construction Estimates, 1884 (Box-volume 248/350)
    - Construction Estimates, 1884 - 1885 (Box-volume 248/351)
  - Other Construction Projects and Unidentified, 1881-1968; Series XXI; 8.5 linear feet and 1 oversize volume